Guide to the Arthur H. Dean papers, 1937-1980
Dean, Arthur H. papers, 1937-1980
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Arthur H. Dean papers, 1937-1980
4100
Arthur H. Dean
146.9 cubic ft.
Correspondence, legal briefs, audio tapes, speeches, research material, pamphlets, clippings, scrapbooks, diaries.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Arthur Hobson Dean was an Ithaca native, Cornell alumnus, lawyer, U.S. government official, diplomat, executive, international and corporate law specialist, and writer.
CHRONOLOGY
1921 B.A. Cornell University
1923 L.L.B. Cornell University Law School
1945-70 Member, Cornell University Board of Trustees (Chairman 1948-70)
1929-50 Partner, law firm of Sullivan and Cromwell, New York
1950-70 Senior Partner, Sullivan and Cromwell
? Vice Chairman of the Board of Trustees of the State University of New York
1953 Chief U.S. negotiator in preliminary Korean War Armistice negotiations at Panmonjom
1958, 1960 Leader of U.S. delegations at the International Law of the Sea Conference
1956-70 Member of the Association for the Promotion and Protection of Private Foreign Investments
? Chairman of the U.S. Delegation to the Conference on Discontinuance of Nuclear Weapons Tests
? Chairman of the U.S. delegation of the Conference of the Committee on Disarmament
? Chairman of the U.S. delegation to the Strategic Arms Limitation Talks
? Delegate to the General Assembly of the United Nations
1946-74 Member of the Foreign Policy Association, Japan Society, Inc.
1956-74 Member of the Asia Society
1954-75 Member of the Asia Foundation
? Member of the Fund for Peaceful Atomic Development, Inc
1955-66 Chairman of the Committee for an Effective and Durable Peace in Asia
1955-75 Member of the Board of Directors of the Council on Foreign Relations, Inc. (member since 1937)
? Member of the American, New York State, and New York City Bar Associations
1963-75 Member of the Lawyer's Committee for Civil Rights Under Law
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence and other papers relate to Dean's activities as an alumnus of Cornell University (B.A. 1921) and Cornell University Law School (L.L.B. 1923); as member of the Cornell University Board of Trustees (1945-70) and Chairman of the Board of Trustees (1948-70); as Partner (1929-50) and Senior Partner (1950-70) in the New York law firm of Sullivan and Cromwell; as Vice Chairman of the Board of Trustees of the State University of New York; as chief U.S. negotiator in preliminary Korean War Armistice negotiations at Panmonjom (1953); as leader of U.S. delegations at the International Law of the Sea Conference (1958, 1960); as member of the Association for the Promotion and Protection of Private Foreign Investments (1956-70); as chairman of the U.S. delegation to the Conference on Discontinuance of Nuclear Weapons Tests; as chairman of the U.S. delegation of the Conference of the Committee on Disarmament; as chairman of the U.S. delegation to the Strategic Arms Limitation Talks; as delegate to the General Assembly of the United Nations; as member of the Foreign Policy association, Japan Society, Inc. (1946-74), Asia Society (1956-74), Asia Foundation (1954-75), and the Fund for Peaceful Atomic Development, Inc.; as chairman of the Committee for an Effective and Durable Peace in Asia (1955-66); as member of the Board of directors of the Council on Foreign Relations, Inc. (1955-75, and member since 1937); as member of the American, New York State, and New York City Bar Associations; and as member of the Lawyer's Committee for Civil Rights Under Law (1963-75).
Major issues include the defense of several U.S. corporations against the Securities Exchange Commission, negotiation of nuclear weapons test ban and disarmament, international commerce laws, European recovery, post war American foreign policy, civil rights under law, federal and state legislation, and the funding of higher education.
Major organizations and companies include: Standard Oil, El Paso, Goldman, Sachs, & Co., and the New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Dean, Arthur Hobson, 1898-; Cornell University. Board of Trustees.; Cornell University--Libraries.; Sullivan & Cromwell.; State University of New York.; Association for the Promotion and Protection of Private Foreign Investments.; Conference of the Discontinuance of Nuclear Weapons Tests.; United Nations.; Foreign Policy Association.; Asia Society.; Asia Foundation.; Council on Foreign Relations.; Association of the Bar of the City of New York.
Subjects:
Bilderberg Meetings.; Korean War.; Libraries.
Places:
Ithaca (N.Y.); Tompkins County (N.Y.)
Form and Genre Terms:
Reminiscences.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Personal
Boxes 1, 2, 79-83, 156-158
Series II. Diaries
Boxes 3, 4
Series III. Speeches/Articles
Boxes 5-13
Series IV. Cornell University
Boxes 14-31, 140-141
Series V. Subject Files
Boxes 32-78; 84-139; 142-155
Nuclear Test Ban Treaty
Disarmament
American Institute of Pacific Relations
Committee for an Effective and Durable Peace in Asia
Korea
Japan Society
Asia Society
Asia Foundation
Association for the Promotion and Protection of Private Foreign Investments (APPI)
Council on Foreign Relations, Inc.
Foreign Affairs, President Johnson's Panel of Consultants on
English Speaking Union of the United States
Bilderberg
Law of the Sea, Department of State Advisory Panel on
State University of New York Board of Trustees
European Recovery (World War II)
United National Association of the United States of America
White House
Nantucket Sound Island Trust-Bill
American Bar Association
New York State Bar Association
New York City Bar Association
American Law Institute
Lawyer's Committee for Civil Rights Under Law
Sullivan and Cromwell - includes U.S. v. Stanley Morgan, et al; El Paso; Standard Oil
Teagle Foundation
National Citizens Committee for Community Relations (Civil Rights)
Committee for Corporate Support of American Universities
Twentieth Century Fund
Association for the Aid of Crippled Children
Corporate Directorships
Treaty Powers, Amendment of
Conference on Indian - American Relations
Other Subject Files
Additional Material
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Personal
  - Personal (Box 1-2)
  - Personal: Photo Albums; Panmonjom, Korea Photo Scrap Book, 1953; Mystery Scrap Book (Box 78)
  - Personal: Photo/Scrap Books, 1959-62 (Box 79)
  - Personal: Photo/Scrap Books, 1961-64 (Box 80)
  - Personal: Photo/Scrap Books, 1961-69 (Box 81)
  - Personal: Proposer - Seconder, 1945-70 (Box 82)
  - Personal: Proposer - Seconder, 1970-80 (Box 83)
  - Certificates of award, merit, membership, and honorary degrees (Box 156-158)
- Series II. Diaries
  - Diaries: 1947-62, 1976-78 (Box 3)
  - Diaries: 1963-65 (Box 4)
- Series III. Speeches/Articles
  - Speeches/Articles (Box 5-9)
  - Speeches/Articles: Jan. 1933 - Jun. 1952 (Box 10)
  - Speeches/Articles: Jan. 1953 - Jul. 1956; Business Income Group Material, 1949-51 (Box 11)
  - Speeches/Articles: Oct. 1956 - Feb. 1962 (Box 12)
  - Speeches/Articles: May 1962 - Jan. 1969 (Box 13)
- Series IV. Cornell University
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees, 6/45 - 1/64 (Box 14)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees, 1/64 - 12/68 (Box 15)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees, 1/69 - 6/70; Executive Committee, 7/46 - 12/68 (Box 16)
  - Cornell University: Executive Committee, 12/64 - 12/68; Investment Committee, 6/48 - 12/74; Building and Grounds Committee, 6/47 - 5/68; Acquisition of Country Club Property, 1957 (Box 17)
  - Cornell University: Cornell Dinner, The Links, 12/5/57; Olin Library Building Project, 3/50 - 7/66; Building Projects, general correspondence 1947 - (Box 18)
  - Cornell University: Building Projects, general correspondence 1947 -; Board of Trustees, committees of the board (Box 19)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees, committees of the board (Box 20)
  - Cornell University: Cornell University Council, Centennial Development Program, 1959 - 66 (Box 21)
  - New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center: Joint Administrative Board 1946 -; Joint Operating Agreement; Agreements of Affiliation (Box 22)
  - Cornell University: General Correspondence (Box 23)
  - Cornell University: Endowment Funds 1945-; Uses: Capital gains, Classification of Funds (Box 24)
  - Cornell University: Endowment Funds - Uses: Contract Dining and Deferred Rushing, 1953-70; Cary Correspondence, 1967-70; 10-year Financial Report, 1937-47; 13-year Financial Report, 1937-50; President's Report 1966-67 (Box 25)
  - Cornell University: Aeronautical Laboratory; Ad Hoc Committee on CAL, 1946-68; Sale of CAL, 1972; Lefkowitz v. Cornell (Box 26)
  - Cornell University: Campus Unrest, 1969; City Council - non-discrimination in Medical College, 1946 (Box 27)
  - Cornell University: Greater New York Committee, 1946-51; General Correspondence, 1951 -; Development Program, 1965 -; Alumni Association; Common Market Conference Council, 1962-63 (Box 28)
  - Cornell University: By-Laws Relating to Cornell (Box 29)
  - Cornell University: Special Gifts to Cornell and Miscellaneous Will Provisions, 1949-; Alumni News, President Reports, and Associated Financial Material (Box 30)
  - Cornell University: Gifts; Financial Committee Budgets (Box 31)
  - Committee for Corporate Support of American Universities: Bound reports; Higher Education for American Democracy; Harvard University Center for International Affairs; Medical Education (CU Medical, NY); Cornell University Law; Cornell History (regional); Additional material (Box 140)
  - Cornell Medical Center, N.Y. (Box 141)
- Series V. Subject Files
  - Nuclear Test Ban Treaty
    - Nuclear Test Ban Negotiations: Press clippings, 12/1/58 - 4/26/62 (Box 32)
    - Nuclear Test Ban Negotiations: Press clippings, 4/27/62 - 9/1/63 (Box 33)
    - Nuclear Test Ban Negotiations: Press clippings, 9/17/63 - 5/15/64 (Box 34)
    - Nuclear Test Ban Negotiations: Press clippings, 5/18/64 - 1/25/65 (Box 35)
    - Nantucket Island Sound Trust Bill (Kennedy Bill): Transcripts of Proceedings (Senate Hearing) (Box 36)
    - Kennedy Bill DebateCassette Tapes, TR-6993a; Cassette Tape
    - Nuclear Test Ban Negotiations: Press clippings, 1/26/65 - 4/29/66 (Box 37)
    - Nuclear Test Ban Negotiations: Press clippings, 1/4/67 - 11/5/69; 18-Nation Disarmament Conference (Box 43)
    - Fund For a Peaceful Atomic Development, Inc., 1954-66; Fund for the Republic, Inc., 1953-55 (Box 45)
    - Nuclear Test Ban Negotiations: Correspondence, 1960-69; Clippings, 1970-73; Crank Letters (Box 46)
    - Nuclear Test Ban Negotiations: Treaty Manuscripts; Outside material (Box 47)
    - Nuclear Test Ban Negotiations, 1961-62; Correspondence, 1970-73; Educational Committee to Halt Nuclear Weapons Spread, 1969-71; Committee to Maintain a Prudent Defense Policy, (ABM Debate) 1969-70 (Box 48)
  - Disarmament
    - Disarmament Reports: Conference of the Committee on Disarmament; Final Records of Conference of the Committee on Disarmament (records of meetings are numbered) (Box 38)
    - Disarmament Reports: Conference of the Committee on Disarmament; Final Records of Conference of the Committee on Disarmament (records of meetings are numbered); The Nature of Radioactive Fallout and its Affect on Man, Parts I & II (Box 39)
    - Disarmament Subject Files: Aggression; Anti-Ballistic Missiles; Communist China and Arms Control; Military Balance and National Security; On-Site Inspection; Peacekeeping Proposals; Production of Fissionable Material for Weapons Purposes; Nuclear Test Ban Treaty (copy) (Box 40)
    - Arthur Dean Disarmament Book: Correspondence; Letters of Comment; Reviews; Manuscripts/Drafts, 1963-64; 1 copy each, Spanish and English (Box 41)
    - Arthur Dean Disarmament Book: Manuscripts 1965; Nuclear Test Ban Negotiations; Press clippings, 5/2/66 - 12/22/66 (Box 42)
    - Disarmament Subject Files: Nuclear Proliferation; Strategic Arms Limitation Talks (SALT); Space Treaty; Underground Test Detection (Box 44)
    - Disarmament: Disarmament Conference, clippings; Personal File - Geneva; Nuclear Test Ban Negotiations; Cooper Resolution; Commitments to Foreign Powers, 1967 (Box 49)
  - American Institute of Pacific Relations
    - American Institute of Pacific Relations: Communist Allegations, 1945-57; Fund Raising; Minutes of Board of Trustees (Box 50)
    - American Institute of Pacific Relations: General; Executive Committee; Board of Trustees; McCarran Committee Hearings, 1942-55 (Box 51)
  - Committee for an Effective and Durable Peace in Asia
    - Committee for an Effective and Durable Peace in Asia: Correspondence, 1965-70; New York Times Advertisement, 1965; Form Letters and Lists of Responses; Coupon Responses, Aa - Az (Box 52)
    - Committee for an Effective and Durable Peace in Asia: Coupon Responses, B - S (Box 53)
    - Committee for an Effective and Durable Peace in Asia: Coupon Responses, T - Z; Fund Raising Correspondence; Financial and Tax Records, 1965-70 (Box 54)
  - Korea
    - Korea: Press clippings and reference material gathered for 1968 speech. (Box 55)
    - Korea: 1953 and following (Box 56)
  - Japan Society
    - The Japan Society, Inc., 1948-74 (Box 57)
  - Asia Society
    - Asia Society: 1956-71 (Box 58)
    - Asia Society: 1971-74 (Box 59)
    - Asia Society: Barnet/Raskin Manuscripts; Blum Manuscript; Young Manuscript; Dulles Manuscript (Box 60)
  - Asia Foundation
    - Asia Foundation: 1974-75 (Box 60)
    - Asia Foundation: 1954-70 (Box 61)
  - Association for the Promotion and Protection of Private Foreign Investments (APPI)
    - APPI: General Papers, 1958-62 (Box 62)
    - APPI: General Papers, 1962-66 (Box 63)
    - APPI: General Papers, 1966-74; Stikker Report; LaBrea y Perinas Papers, 1964-69 (Box 64)
    - APPI: Correspondence, 1958-76 (Box 65)
    - APPI: Committee for Effective Use of International Court by Repeal of Self-Judging Reservation, (Connally Amendment) 1960-66; National Committee for International Development, (Foreign Aid) 1965-66; The Atlantic Council, 1965-75 (Box 66)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc.
    - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc.: Board of Directors, 1955-75 (Box 67)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc.: General, 1937-73; Directors Policy Group, 1960; William Bundy Appointment as Editor of Foreign Affairs, 1971; Grand jury Subpoena for Ellsberg Paper, 1971; Foreign Affairs - Book-of-the-Month-Club, 1959-69; Committee on Bequests and Endowments, 1957; Capital Fund Drive, 1966-75; Committee on Studies, 1951-69 (Box 68)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc.: Norwegian Nobel Institute Conference on Western Democracies and World Problem; Committee on Membership, 1956-73 (Box 69)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc. Discussion and Study Groups: Security Agreements in the Far East, 1956-60; Russian Group, 1945-48; Draft General Report on Soviet-American Relations, 1952-59; Sino-Soviet Relations, 1955-57 (Box 70)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc. Discussion and Study Groups: German Unity, 1952; France, 1945; Poland, 1945; Western Europe, 1945-57; Argentina, Brazil, and Mexico, 1944-45; Southern Africa: The Place of South African Problems in American Foreign Policy, 1967; Africa: Emerging Problems of African Foreign Policy, 1953-57; Postwar Economic Aspects of American Foreign Policy, 1942-46; Propaganda and Foreign Policy, 1947; Princeton Conference on Foreign Programs of Studies, 1945; Strategic Bases and Alliances, 1958; United Nations Foreign Policy, 1957-59; Ad Hoc Group on Report to Senate Committee on Foreign Relations, 1959; Power and Policy, 1963; Re-examination of American Foreign Policy, 1966-67; Role of the American Ambassador, 1963-64; Ambassador Douglas MacArthur Dinner, 1960 (Box 71)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc. Discussion and Study Groups: American Policy in Middle East, 1951-56; Neutralism in Asia, 1957-58; Southeast Asia as a Focus of World Politics, 1966-67; Conference on Indian-American Relations, 1956; U.S.-Indian Relations, 1954-57; India and Pakistan, 1966; Spain and the U.S. 1958-59 (Box 72)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc. Discussion and Study Groups and Steering Committee: Far Eastern Affairs - American Policy in the Far East (China, Japan, Korea, etc.) 1945-51; American Chinese Group, 1944; Chinese Communist Policy, 1954-55; Communist China and U.S. Policy in Asia, 1958-60; China and the Far East, 1962-67; Taiwan and the Nationalist Government, 1964; American Cultural Relations with Japan, 1952-54 (Box 73)
  - Foreign Affairs, President Johnson's Panel of Consultants on
    - President Lyndon B. Johnson's Panel of Consultants on Foreign Affairs: Correspondence, 1964-69; General Papers on: Communist China; India-Pakistan; NATO; U.S.S.R.; Vietnam (Box 74)
  - English Speaking Union of the United States
    - The English-Speaking Union of the United States: Correspondence, 1959-66; Minutes, 1959-74 (Box 75)
  - Bilderberg
    - Bilderberg: 1962-68 (Box 76)
    - Bilderberg: 1968-80; American Friends of Bilderberg, Inc., 1973-79 (Box 77)
  - Law of the Sea, Department of State Advisory Panel on
    - Department of State Advisory Panel: International Law, 1970-73 Law of the Sea, 1970-76 (Box 84)
    - Law of the Sea: Correspondence and Documents on U.N. Conference on Law of the Sea, 1958 and 1960 (Box 85)
    - Law Of the Sea: Third United Nations, Conference on Law of the Sea, Session at Caracas, Venezuela, 1974 (Box 86)
    - Law of the Sea: Far East Trip, 1960; Correspondence and Documents, 1961-69; Oil and Gas Documents, 1965 (Box 87)
    - Department of State Advisory Panel: Law of the Sea, 1970-76 (Box 88)
    - Law of the Sea: Maps, 1958 Conference (Box 89)
  - State University of New York Board of Trustees
    - State University of New York Board of Trustees, 1949-53 (Box 90)
    - State University of New York Board of Trustees: Committee on Medical Education Centers, 1950; Minutes, 1948-52; Budgets, 1951-53 (Box 91)
  - European Recovery (World War II)
    - Recovery, (World War II): Documents re Foreign Assets Control, including White Paper and Reports on Dutch Economy; Federal Reserve Regulations re Defense Production, etc.; Reconstruction Finance Corporation Reports, 1945-50; Articles and Reports on Postwar Economy; Background on International Bank for Reconstruction and Development; Marshall Plan, 1946-48 (Box 92)
    - Recovery (World War II): Neutrality Act of 1939; Renegotiation of War Contracts; Hearings on Manpower, 1942-43; Reports and Hearings on Mobilization and Postwar Economics; Hearings on Extension of Reciprocal Trade Agreements Act, 1943; Proclaimed List of Certain Blocked Nationals, 1945 (Box 93)
    - Recovery (World War II): Bound material (Box 94)
    - European Recovery: Bound Material (Box 111)
  - United Nations Association of the United States of America
    - United Nations Association of the U.S.A.: General, 1964-75; International Cooperation year (Box 95)
    - United Nations Association of the U.S.A.: China Panel, 1966-67; Pamphlets (Box 96)
  - White House
    - White House: Arms Control and Disarmament Agency; Atomic Energy Commission; LOS Document Log (Box 97)
    - White House (Box 98)
  - Nantucket Sound Island Trust-Bill
    - Nantucket Sound Trust-Bill: Related Legislation; Correspondence; Newspaper Clippings; Maps (Box 99)
    - Nantucket Sound Trust-Bill: Legislative History Correspondence (Box 100)
    - Nantucket Sound Trust Bill: Planting Fields Foundation, 1964 - 79 (Box 123)
    - Islands Trust Bill Debate, March 30, 1976; TR-6992a
  - American Bar Association
    - Special and Standing Committees of American Bar Association: Standing Committee on Education Against Communism, 1966-67 (Dean not a member); Advisory Committee to Cooperate With the World Peace Through Law Center, 1969 ABA Sections: Section of Antitrust Law, 1951-67; Section of Public Utility Law, 1951-59; Section of Corporation, Banking, and Business Law: Committee on Money, Credit, and Monetary; Policy (Dean Chairman) 1960-63 Section of International and Comparative Law, including: General - 1946-67; Council - 1954-58; Special Committee to Study the Council: Dirksen Bill, 1955; Membership Committee, 1958-59; Special Committee on Cooperation with Legal Profession of Friendly Nations, 1955-60; Banco and Sabbatino cases, 1966-67; Committee on Collaboration between Executive and Legislative Branches of Federal Government 1954-60; Committee on Law of the Sea, 1959-60 (Dean not a member) (Box 101)
    - American Bar Association Meetings for which Dean was a Member of House of Delegates: Union International Des Avocats - Paris, July 15-20, 1956; 1956 Annual Meeting, Dallas, Texas; 1956 Mid-Year Meeting, Chicago, Illinois; 1957 Annual Meeting, New York and London; 1958 Mid-Year Meeting, Atlanta, Georgia; 1958 Annual Meeting, Los Angeles, California; American College of Trial Lawyers; General 1970-74; Committee for Investigating Money on Hand in Checking and Savings Accounts, 1960-61; New York Law Institute; General, 1955-62 (Box 102)
    - Special and Standing Committees of the American Bar Association: Committee on Judicial Salaries, 1944-45; Association and Advisory Committee to the 1955-56 Standing committee of Public Relations, 1956-60; Committee on Federal Judiciary, 1956 (Dean not a member); Standing Committee on Peace and Law Through the United Nations (Dean Chairman) 1958-61; Special Committee on World Peace Through Law (Dean Vice Chairman) 1958-65 (Box 103)
    - American Bar Association: General, 1956-75; Space Law Advisory Committee, 1964-70 (Box 105)
  - New York State Bar Association
    - New York State Bar Association: Committee on Corporation Law, 1939-43 (Box 104)
    - New York State Bar Association: Antitrust Section: Committee on Sherman Law, 1950-56; Banking Law Section, 1952-64; Committee on Federal Constitution, 1956-64; Committee on Amendment to Federal Constitution, 1954-57; Subcommittee on World Peace through Law, 1959 (Box 105)
    - New York State Bar Association: Committee on Corporation Law, 1944-51 (Box 106)
    - New York State Bar Association: Committee on Corporation Law, 1951-54; Committee on Federal Legislation, 1943-44 (Box 107)
  - New York City Bar Association
    - Association of the Bar of the City of New York: General, 1946-68 American Judicature Society: General, 1956-64 American Society of International Law: General, 1955-64; Executive Committee, 1956-75; Consultative Committee, 1960-61; Committee on Financing and Endowment, 1959-72 Inter-American Bar Association: General, 1960-65 International Law Association: General, 1946-64; Fund Raising for 55th Conference, New York, 1972 (Box 108)
    - Association of the Bar of the City of New York: Committee on Federal Legislation, 1943-50; Executive Committee, 1945-47; Solicitation Of Funds for Committee in Defense of Constitution (Bricker Amendment) 1954-57; Committee on Increase of Membership. 1957-58; Committee on International Law, 1946-58; Committee on the Judiciary, 1955-58; Nominating Committee, 1956 (Box 109)
    - Association of the Bar of the City of New York: Committee on Federal Legislation, 1938-43 (Box 110)
  - American Law Institute
    - American Law Institute: General, 1955-75; Private Corporate Law, 1949; Investment Committee, 1968-73 (Box 112)
  - Lawyer's Committee for Civil Rights Under Law
    - Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under Law: Mississippi Project, 1965-74; General, 1972-75 (Box 113)
    - Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under Law: Israel Correspondence (Box 114)
    - Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under Law: General, 1963-68 (Box 115)
    - Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under Law: General, 1968-71 (Box 116)
  - Sullivan and Cromwell
    - U.S. v Stanley Morgan et al. (Box 117-122)
    - Sullivan and Cromwell: Bound briefs and case material (Box 124125)
    - El Paso: Bound briefs and case material (Box 126-128)
    - Standard Oil: Bound briefs and case material (Box 129-130)